<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newsfeeds on Marsettler</title>
    <link>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newsfeeds on Marsettler</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsfeed 2025</title>
      <link>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2025/</guid>
      <description>June 2025 Boomerang by Kung Fun No (Translated from Korean)  When I told someone from headquarters that I had returned, they didn&#39;t ask any questions and simply said, &amp;ldquo;Thanks for coming back.&amp;rdquo; Then they immediately moved on to the next topic. That day, I kept thinking about those words. My heart felt warm, I was glad I came back, and I felt motivated to do even better going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsfeed 2024</title>
      <link>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2024/</guid>
      <description>December 2024 2024년 CTO 회고 by 향로  대부분의 회사가 그렇겠지만, 퇴사하는 팀원을 막는 것은 대단히 어려운 일이다. 그래서 팀원의 근속 기간을 늘리는 것도 중요하지만, 팀원이 빠르게 적응해서 기여 기간을 늘리는 것이 훨씬 제어가능하다.
  Like most companies, preventing a team member from leaving is extremely difficult. Therefore, while increasing the retention period of team members is important, enabling them to adapt quickly and extend their contribution period is much more manageable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsfeed 2023</title>
      <link>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2023/</guid>
      <description>December 2023 The Big Cloud Exit FAQ by @dhh  This isn’t some archaic knowledge that’s been lost to the ages. We might not know exactly how the pyramids were built, but we do still know how to connect a Linux machine to the internet.
 I think many of us are forgetting this.
 &amp;ldquo;buy the baseline, rent the spike&amp;rdquo;
 100% agree.
Constant Propagation in Compiler Design  In simpler words, we can say that if some value is assigned a known constant, than we can simply replace the that value by constant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsfeed 2022</title>
      <link>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2022/</guid>
      <description>December 2022 Guido van Rossum: Python and the Future of Programming | Lex Fridman Podcast #341  GitHub Copilot   Are programmers jobs threatend by the existence of stack overflow? I don&#39;t think so.
 Agreed.
If it is truly important to you, you’ll find a way; if it is not, you’ll find an excuse. - anonymous 2022년 10월 중대한 결정을 지혜롭계 하는 법 일단 마음 내키는대로 결정하고, 그 뒤에 벌어질 일들을 담대하게 마주하라</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>뉴스피드 2021</title>
      <link>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2021/</guid>
      <description>2020년 7월  승진은 후불제 &amp;hellip; 이미 다음 단계 일은 하고 있음 + 그걸 얼마나 잘 당연시하는가
 쑤(@sajiiinnn) 님의 트윗
2020년 6월  끝으로 어느 팀이든 좋은 코드를 마스터한 시니어만으로 구성되지 않는다. 프로그래밍팀은 하나의 마을이다. 거기엔 아름답고 웅장하게 세워진 성도 있고 이제 첫 삽을 떠본 주니어가 만든 초가집도 있다. 시니어의 역할은 주니어의 초가집 엉성한 부분을 지적하는것에서 끝나지 않는다. 진짜 마스터는 계속해서 자기 성을 짓는 사람이다. 주니어가 지켜보며 영감 (inspiration)을 얻을만큼 계속해서 조금 더 아름다운 성을 만드는 사람이다.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>뉴스피드 2020</title>
      <link>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://marsettler.com/newsfeed/newsfeed-2020/</guid>
      <description>2020년 12월 Disagree and commit 이병준님의 면접시 조심하면 좋은 것들 중 일부
링크: https://youtu.be/SZEHjcDSEdE?t=183
 자기가 동의하지 않는 내용이라도 팀원의 한 사람으로서 동의를 했다면 그 동의한 내용을 반드시 따라야 한다.
 기계인간님의 개발자의 성격 이야기 어떤 역할을 하느냐에 따라 조금씩 다르겠지만, 개발자도 적극적이어야 할 필요가 있다는 점에서 크게 공감합니다.
 사람마다 회사생활하며 느낀바는 다르겠지만 개발자는 어느 수준부터는 축구선수같길 요구받는다. 내가 수비수라고 수비만 하면 안된다. 내가 공격해야 하는 상황일 땐 공 차고 나가면서 골도 넣을 수 있어야 한다.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>